{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "I want to dress up as a princess .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is funny to see all the costumes .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "We went to China to see the Great Wall .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am going out to walk the dog .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to stay at home tonight and watch TV .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "My brother goes to the park to play football .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "They want to move to Australia in May .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hope to see him tomorrow .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "She plans to visit Spain next month .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I opened the curtains to see the street .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "My biggest wish is to go on holidays .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to buy flowers for my mother .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I need to see a doctor .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I went to the shop to buy some food .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hope to find my cat today .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to buy a car next week .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "They are going to London to see the Big Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "We went to the cinema to watch a film .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "He wants to eat some cake .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "We're planning to go to New York .",
      "correctAnswer": "Infinitive",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Gerund"
    },
    {
      "question": "I like getting up early in the morning .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "My father started working as a lawyer yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "They talked about getting a new car .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "Buying Christmas presents is my favourite activity .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "My sister is scared of being alone at night .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mom is tired from working all day .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "He was happy about winning the game .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "Thanks for inviting me for your birthday party !",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hate waking up early .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I love eating biscuits .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I finished doing my homework five minutes ago .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I started running two years ago .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I brush my teeth before going to bed .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm going for a walk after finishing this test .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I don't like going to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hate watching horror movies .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I started reading a new book yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "Drawing is my hobby .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I haven't finished running yet .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I like going to the park .",
      "correctAnswer": "Gerund",
      "incorrectAnswers": "Infinitive"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "I want _____ # up as a princess .",
      "correctAnswer": "to dress",
      "incorrectAnswers": "dressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is funny _____ # all the costumes .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "We went to China _____ # the Great Wall .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am going out _____ # the dog .",
      "correctAnswer": "to walk",
      "incorrectAnswers": "walking"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want _____ # at home tonight and watch TV .",
      "correctAnswer": "to stay",
      "incorrectAnswers": "staying"
    },
    {
      "question": "My brother goes to the park _____ # football .",
      "correctAnswer": "to play",
      "incorrectAnswers": "playing"
    },
    {
      "question": "They want _____ # to Australia in May .",
      "correctAnswer": "to move",
      "incorrectAnswers": "moving"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hope _____ # him tomorrow .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "She plans _____ # Spain next month .",
      "correctAnswer": "to visit",
      "incorrectAnswers": "visiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "I opened the curtains _____ # the street .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "My biggest wish is _____ # on holidays .",
      "correctAnswer": "to go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "going"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want _____ # flowers for my mother .",
      "correctAnswer": "to buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "buying"
    },
    {
      "question": "I need _____ # a doctor .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "I went to the shop _____ # some food .",
      "correctAnswer": "to buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "buying"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hope _____ # my cat today .",
      "correctAnswer": "to find",
      "incorrectAnswers": "finding"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want _____ # a car next week .",
      "correctAnswer": "to buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "buying"
    },
    {
      "question": "They are going to London _____ # the Big Ben .",
      "correctAnswer": "to see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "We went to the cinema _____ # a film .",
      "correctAnswer": "to watch",
      "incorrectAnswers": "watching"
    },
    {
      "question": "He wants _____ # some cake .",
      "correctAnswer": "to eat",
      "incorrectAnswers": "eating"
    },
    {
      "question": "We're planning _____ # to New York .",
      "correctAnswer": "to go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "going"
    },
    {
      "question": "I like _____ # up early in the morning .",
      "correctAnswer": "getting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to get"
    },
    {
      "question": "My father started _____ # as a lawyer yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "They talked about _____ # a new car .",
      "correctAnswer": "getting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to get"
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ # Christmas presents is my favourite activity .",
      "correctAnswer": "Buying",
      "incorrectAnswers": "To buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "My sister is scared of _____ # alone at night .",
      "correctAnswer": "being",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mom is tired from _____ # all day .",
      "correctAnswer": "working",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "He was happy about _____ # the game .",
      "correctAnswer": "winning",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to win"
    },
    {
      "question": "Thanks for _____ # me for your birthday party !",
      "correctAnswer": "inviting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to invite"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hate _____ # up early .",
      "correctAnswer": "waking",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to wake"
    },
    {
      "question": "I love _____ # biscuits .",
      "correctAnswer": "eating",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "I finished _____ # my homework five minutes ago .",
      "correctAnswer": "doing",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to do"
    },
    {
      "question": "I started _____ # two years ago .",
      "correctAnswer": "running",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to run"
    },
    {
      "question": "I brush my teeth before _____ # to bed .",
      "correctAnswer": "going",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm going for a walk after _____ # this test .",
      "correctAnswer": "finishing",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "I don't like _____ # to school .",
      "correctAnswer": "going",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hate _____ # horror movies .",
      "correctAnswer": "watching",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "I started _____ # a new book yesterday .",
      "correctAnswer": "reading",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to read"
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ # is my hobby .",
      "correctAnswer": "Drawing",
      "incorrectAnswers": "To draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "I haven't finished _____ # yet .",
      "correctAnswer": "running",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to run"
    },
    {
      "question": "I like _____ # to the park .",
      "correctAnswer": "going",
      "incorrectAnswers": "to go"
    }
  ]
}